http://www.ambitenergy.com/privacy

Contact Ambit
Esp.
Our Companywide Privacy Commitment to You
If you are a California Resident:
Please review the privacy policy for California residents for information about your specific rights regarding your personal information.
We understand the importance of safeguarding your personal information. At Ambit Energy, we are committed to protecting your personal information as you use our website. We would like to let you know that Ambit Energy does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone, unless such information is provided to us voluntarily and knowingly, except as otherwise provided in this Policy.
We only collect personal information for specific purposes, including providing you with retail energy service. We will not sell or make your personal information available to unaffiliated companies for commercial purposes unrelated to the business of Ambit Energy. However, we may use this information to inform you about goods or services that may interest you.
Ambit Energy will not disclose any information about you to unaffiliated companies or organizations without your consent, except as disclosed to you in this Policy, unless: (a) we are required to do so by law; (b) we believe it necessary to respond to an inquiry or provide you with a requested service; (c) It is necessary to make good on the Terms of Service Agreement we have entered into with you; or (d) to protect the rights, property or personal safety of any other person, including another Ambit Energy Customer or any member of the public.
Ambit Energy and its affiliates recognize that by utilizing our website, you are placing trust in us. We thank you, and we will take precautions to protect your information. In order to operate our Website and deliver retail electric service, we may share your personal information with a service partner under strict conditions. We will not otherwise disclose your personal information to other companies without your explicit consent.
You are not required to register or provide information to us in order to view a large majority of our site. However, to obtain services from Ambit Energy or to access portions of our Website – including, but not limited to – Ambit Energy’s “Power Zone”, “Customer Login” or other services provided by Ambit Energy, you may be asked to provide personal information. We use your information to personalize your online experience or to provide you with requested services. Ambit Energy will only use your information in strict accordance with this Policy.
How We Protect Your Information
We will endeavor to take all steps deemed reasonable by Ambit Energy in order to keep any information we hold about you as secure as possible. Your information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. We require our employees and data processors to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by Ambit Energy.
The company takes many precautions, including administrative and technical measures, to protect your personal information against theft, mishandling and loss. Additionally, Ambit protects against misuse of your information – such as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal information. Due to the nature of the Internet, no one, including Ambit Energy, can give absolute assurance that your information will be secure 100% of the time. Ambit Energy will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information.
Ambit Energy uses appropriate, commercially available anti-virus software to ensure that this website does not contain or carry viruses. However, due to the rapidly developing nature of viruses and the Internet, we strongly recommend that you employ similar anti-virus software when accessing the Ambit Energy website. Ambit Energy makes no warranty that the website or e-mail correspondence is free from such viruses.
Children
Our website contains educational, energy-related information that may be of interest to children. Ambit Energy does not seek to gather personal information online from or about children under the age of 13. The company encourages all children and young teens to ask their parents for authorization before providing any information about themselves or their household to anyone over the Internet.
Data Collection
Ambit may use “cookie” technology on our Website. “Cookies” are small text files used by a website to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s access to and use of the site, and to track behavior on the website pages you visit, among other uses. Our website may automatically collect Cookies and other information – including, but not limited to, your domain name. Ambit may compile aggregate data for statistical purposes, in order to improve our content of our website or to better administer the web pages available on the Ambit Energy website.
When and if Ambit Energy requests an email address from you, you will be given the opportunity to indicate whether or not you wish to receive future email solicitations from us. Regardless, from time to time we may send you emails for other reasons, including, but not limited to, servicing your energy account with us.
Privacy Questions
This website is owned and operated by Ambit Energy. This Privacy Policy has been established to provide you with assurance concerning your personal information, and to explain our policy concerning the protection and use of your information.
If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at (877) 282-6248, Monday through Friday, 8:00 a.m. – 6:00 p.m., Saturday, 10:00 a.m. – 5:00 p.m. CT, or write to us at:
Ambit Energy
P.O. Box 864589
Plano, TX
75086
Attn: Compliance Department
If you would like to know what information Ambit retains or if you wish to have Ambit change your information because it is out of date or inaccurate, please contact us at (877) 282-6248, Monday through Friday, 8:00 a.m. – 6:00 p.m., Saturday, 10:00 a.m. – 5:00 p.m. CT, and we will modify your records accordingly.
Contact Ambit
Contact Ambit Energy
Careers at Ambit Energy
Satisfaction Guarantee
Site Map
Terms of Use
Privacy
Glossary of Bill Terms
Satisfaction Guarantee
© 2020 Ambit Energy. All rights reserved.
Licensed in
CA,
CT,
DC,
DE,
IL,
IN,
MA,
MD,
ME,
NH,
NJ,
NY,
OH,
PA,
RI,
TX
&
VA.
(CA #CTA0037, DC #GA11-8-6, MD #IR-1992, MD #IR-1993, NJ #GSL-0110, NJ #ESL-0111, TX #10117).
Connecticut Past Variable Rates,
Delaware Next Cycle Rate,
Illinois Next Cycle Rate,
Maryland Next Cycle Rate,
Massachusetts Next Cycle Rate,
New Hampshire Next Cycle Rate
Direct Selling Association Member
For more information on DSA visit: DSA's Code of Ethics, www.dsef.org and www.directselling411.com   |   Toll-Free (877) 282-6248, P.O. Box 864589, Plano, TX 75086
Customer Login/Pay Bill
Consultant Login
Ambit Energy Home
Español
Ambit on Facebook
Ambit on Twitter
Ambit on Instagram
Ambit on YouTube
